The tricky thing about Joins is that there are a means to do other types of analysis.
Join 的复杂性在于可以做各种不同类型的分析
Combining data isn't an end unto itself.
整合数据本身并不是它的最终目的
It's a tool that allows you to filter or aggregate with an expanded set of information.
它只是一种工具 让你能筛选或整合一个扩充的信息集
That means queries involving joins can get pretty complicated.
这也意味着涉及查询的 Join 可能会非常复杂
In order to get the exact results you're after,
要得到你需要的具体结果
you need to be careful about exactly how you filter the data.
你就要非常仔细地考虑如何筛选数据
As with joins, there are multiple options.
而使用 Join 的话 你就有多种选择
To illustrate this, let's take a look at
为了说明这一点
all the orders that were brought in by one particular sales rep.
现在让我们来看看由一个销售代表带来的所有订单
Imagine yourself as a sales manager at Parch and Posey.
假设你是 Parch &amp; Posey 的一名销售经理
You'd like to make it easy for a sales rep to find her own deals rather than
你当然希望你的销售代表能轻松地找到自己完成的交易
having to sift through all the orders and try and remember which were hers.
而不是要查阅所有订单 回忆哪些是自己完成的
Remember, sales rep ID isn't in the Orders table,
要记住 订单表格中没有销售代表 ID
so join isn't necessary to get that information.
所以不需要通过 Join 来得到此信息
The first way to filter this data is something we're
筛选这类数据的第一种方法是我们非常熟悉的
already familiar with, the WHERE clause.
WHERE 子句
Let's take our combined orders and accounts tables and filter the results set to
现在我们来找出整合后的订单和账户表格 对结果集进行筛选
contain only the orders booked by sales rep 321500.
找出仅由一位编号 321500 的销售代表完成的订单
As you can see, the only rows in our result
可以看到 结果集中仅包括
set are the rows that fit the criteria in the WHERE clause.
符合 WHERE 子句标准的行
The ones that have a sales rep ID equal to 321500.
即销售代表 ID 为 321500 的行
But, what if we just want to mark all the orders that belong to rep 321500
但是 如果我们想要标记所有由 321500 代表完成的订单
and keep all the other orders in the result set as well?
同时将所有其他订单保留在结果集中呢？
We can do that by filtering in the ON clause.
我们可以通过 ON 子句进行筛选
By changing where to end,
将 WHERE 改为 AND
we're moving this logical statement to become part of the ON clause.
就让这个逻辑语句变为了 ON 子句的一部分
This effectively pre-filters the right table to include only rows with
这样能在连接前有效地对右边表格进行预筛选
sales rep ID 321500 before the join is executed.
仅筛选出销售代表 ID 为 321500 的相关行
In other words, it's like a WHERE clause that applies before the join rather than after.
也就是说 就像是在连接前而不是连接后使用 WHERE 子句一样
You can almost think of this like joining orders to a different table.
你可以把它看成将订单连接至另外一个表格
One that only includes a subset of the rows in the original accounts table.
这个表格只包括最初账户表格某些行的子集
Since this is a left join,
由于这是 Left Join
we'll see a result set that includes all rows from the Orders table as well as
结果集列出的是 订单表格的所有行
any data in this new pre-filtered table that
以及新的预筛选表格中
match with the account ID in the Orders table.
与订单表格中账户 ID 相匹配的数据
As you can see, sales rep 321500 only had a few accounts.
你可以看到 销售代表 321500 只对应少数账户
So, a lot of these orders remain unmatched.
大量订单并没有与之匹配
It might seem frivolous to leave so many orders in this result set without account names.
这个结果集含有大量没有账户名称的订单 看上去似乎没有意义
But, this type of join will be incredibly useful once
但是在下一课学习数据聚合时
you move on to data aggregation in the next lesson.
你会发现这种 Join 出乎意料地有用